## **Pranav Kadam**

T-2, Shree Nidhi Heights, 77, Shukrawar Peth, Satara +91 9561110353

impranav011@gmail.com

Sep 25,2021

CDAC Company Noida

Dear Sir / Madam

As I learned about this opportunity through the placement center and was delight to find that all my skills are accomplished meet all of the necessary requirement, which I was drawn to this exciting opportunity. I would like to apply for this post as I am a software developer more than 5 years of experience.

I believe that my qualification and extensive work experience in installing, maintaining and troubleshooting software system makes me an ideal candidate for your vacancy. About skills as a familiar language are C, Java, JavaScript, Python. I also have good Knowledge of rational database and of developing web services. I have excellent problem-solving skills and the skills needed to help train others on the programs used to enhance productivity.

Your listed requirements closely match my background and skills. A few I would like to highlight that are:

- Graduated in B.E IT from Mumbai university with 8.87 CGPA.
- 5 years of experience in software development and 2 years of experience as product manager.

- Knowledge of technologies like SOLR/Elastic search.
- Highly skilled in designing, testing and developing software.
- In depth knowledge of Core Java, Multi-threading, Spring, Spring-Boot.
- Certification in JavaScript and Object-Oriented technologies.

Please find enclose with this letter with my CV for your consideration. In closing I thank you for your time and I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely,

Pranav Kadam

### **RESUME**

Pranav Kadam T-2, Shree Nidhi Heights, 77, Shukrawar Peth, Satara - 415002 9561110353 | impranav011@gmail.com

## **Career Objective:**

A result-orinted Software Developer With 5+ years of experience seeking a suitable position at a reputed organisation where I can use my extensive knowledge and expertise in software design.development while contributing to the symbolic growth of the organization with the technical,innovative,logical skills and grow as a Software developer.

## **Education Qualifiaction:**

- Completed post Graduation from University of Technology, Mumbai in Advance Information Technology with CGPA 8.3 in 2014.
- Completed Graduation from Pillai college of engineering, New Panvel in Information Technology with CGPA 8.87 in 2012.

# Work Experience:

- Worked as Senior software engineer in LTI from May 2018 to February 2021.
- Worked as Junior software engineer in WIPRO from March 2018 to August 2018.

#### **Technical Skills:**

- Programming Languages Python, Java, PHP, HTML5/CSS, JavaScript
- Knowledge in Web Development tools, Frameworks, Augmented reality
- Frameworks AJAX, ReactJS, NodeJS, Django
- Databases SQL(MySQL, Oracle),AWS
- Tools Unix, Git

#### Courses:

Web development, Database Management Systems, Software Development, Advanced Software Development, Algorithm Design and Analysis Data Structure, Core java, Operating system, web designing.

# **Projects:**

- Hotel Management System(Java, PostgresQL).
- Debugging Software detects and remove existing and potential bugs in software code that can cause it to behave unexpectedly or crash.

### **Achievements:**

- Secured 7<sup>th</sup> rank in Smart India Hackathon:2010-2011
- Completed software development course offered by IIT bombay under the college to coporate:2012

**Declaration:** I hereby certify that all the above mentioned information is true to the best of my knowledge.